# **GUSTAVO H. MIGLIORINI**

# **Data Scientist**

Londrina, Paraná, Brazil +55 19 9 98095841 gustavomig@gmail.com https://gustavomigliorini.netlify.app/

#### **SUMMARY:**

Data Scientist with broad experience in scientific research and programming languages such as R, Python and SQL. A quick learner with the ability to solve problems independently, a critical thinker, and a proactive team player. Previous experience working as a Data Analyst in both corporate and academic environments.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

#### **ALS Life Sciences**

Data Analyst | February, 2022 - December, 2022

- · Analyses of clinical research data
- Validation of statistical results
- Review of statistical reports

### **Federal University of Pernambuco**

Research Data Analyst | May, 2021 - December, 2021

- · Analyses of research data
- Teaching of R programming and statistical analyses
- · Design of research experiments
- Scientific writing and publication

#### **EDUCATION:**

# 2021 - 2022 | Federal University of Technology - Paraná, Brazil

Data Science - Specialist

Capstone project: Identification of birds from Brazil through deep learning for image classification

2014 - 2018 | State University of São Paulo, Brazil

**Environmental Sciences - PhD** 

## **SKILLS:**

- Python
- R language
- SQL
- Power BI
- Machine Learning

#### **CERTIFICATIONS:**

- Python for Data Science, IBM, 2023
- Power BI, Udemy, 2023